A Guide to the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006-2009
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2006-2009., Extent: 8.05 cu. ft. (23 boxes) (Box 7-29)
  - Subseries B: Supporting Documentation, 2006-2009.
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Homeland Security Executive Committee Meeting, 2007 May (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2007 May (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2007 June (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2007 September (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Leaders Seminar, 2007 September (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Emergency Preparedness Council Meeting, 2007 October (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2007 November (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2008 January (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2009 February (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Governor-Governor-Mayor-Secretary Meeting, 2009 September (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Emergency Preparedness Council Meeting, 2009 November (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Homeland Security Funding, Urban Areas Security Initiative [UASI], 2006-2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - National Governors Association, Governors' Homeland Security Advisors Council, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Naval Station Mayport, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk State University, Intelligence Community Center for Academic Excellence, National Advisory Board Meeting, 2007 October (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk State University, Intelligence Community Center for Academic Excellence, National Advisory Board Meeting, 2008 July (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk State University, Intelligence Community Center for Academic Excellence, National Advisory Board Meeting, 2008 October (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Norfolk State University, Intelligence Community Center for Academic Excellence, National Advisory Board Meeting, 2009 February (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Norfolk State University, Intelligence Community Center for Academic Excellence, National Advisory Board Meeting, 2009 October (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Organizational Assessment, Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Outlying Landing Field, Meetings, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Outlying Landing Field, Meetings, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Performance measures, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Area Evacuation and Sheltering Planning, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bill 1046 (REAL ID), 2009 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Senat Bill 1093 (Mutual Aid Agreements), 2009 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Senate Finance Committee, Homeland Security Funding status report, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Analysis and report, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Question and Answers, Groups 1-4, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Question and Answers, Groups 5-10, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Peer Reviews, Groups 1-3, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Peer Reviews, Groups 4-5, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Administration and Agriculture and Forestry, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Commerce and Trade and Finance, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Health and Human Resources and Natural Resources, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Public Safety and Technology, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - State Agency Preparedness Survey, Transporation and Education, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - State Agency Preparedness Report, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - State Role in Nuclear Terrosim Prevention, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Subcommittee on Public Safety, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 1a)
    - Telework Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commission on Immigration, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Fusion Center Advisory Board, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Critical Infrastructure Protection and Resiliency Strategic Plan, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Virginia's Interagency Anti-Gang Workgroup, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Virginia's Interagency Anti-Gang Workgroup, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Virginia's Interoperability Baseline Assessment Report, Interoperability in Virginia, Final report, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Virginia's Interoperability Baseline Assessment Report, Interoperability in Virginia, Executive Summary, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Virginia National Defense Industrial Authority, 2007-2009 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Uniform Statewide Building Code, 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Homeland Security Files - Grants, 2006-2007., Extent: ( boxes)
  - Allocations, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Citizen and Community education in Homeland Security, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - (Box 29)
  - (Box 29)